<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>microbiota on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</title>
    <link>https://examplesite.com/tags/microbiota/</link>
    <description>Recent content in microbiota on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://examplesite.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:48:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://examplesite.com/tags/microbiota/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Altered Maturation of the Skin Bacterial Communities in Infants with Atopic Dermatitis</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35818733/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:48:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35818733/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link DOI
Copyright and License Information Copyright (c) 2022 Caroline M. Olesen, Maja-Lisa Clausen, Tove Agner, Maria Asplund, Linett Rasmussen, Yasemin T. Yüksel, Paal S. Andersen, Thomas Litman, Anders J. Hansen, Christopher J. Barnes
This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.
This is an Open Access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/), allowing third parties to copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format and to remix, transform, and build upon the material for non-commercial purposes, provided proper attribution to the original work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Difference of Gut Microbiota and Their Correlations With Urinary Organic Acids Between Autistic Children With and Without Atopic Dermatitis</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35800387/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:39:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35800387/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Copyright © 2022 Hong, Hou, Xu, Lang, Jin, Zeng, Zhang, Tian and You
This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GW4064 Alters Gut Microbiota Composition and Counteracts Autism-Associated Behaviors in BTBR T&#43;tf/J Mice </title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35811667/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:31:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35811667/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Jiayin Liu, Chuanqi Liu, Zhanyuan Gao, Lianyu Zhou, Junwei Gao, Yi Luo, Tianyao Liu, and Xiaotang Fan
Copyright © 2022 Liu, Liu, Gao, Zhou, Gao, Luo, Liu and Fan This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Characterization of Novel Faecalibacterium prausnitzii Strains Isolated from Healthy Volunteers: A Step Forward in the Use of F. prausnitzii as a Next-Generation Probiotic</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_28713353/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:19:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_28713353/</guid>
      <description>Link to paper
Copyright and License Information Copyright © 2017 Martín, Miquel, Benevides, Bridonneau, Robert, Hudault, Chain, Berteau, Azevedo, Chatel, Sokol, Bermúdez-Humarán, Thomas and Langella.
This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) or licensor are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overlapping Mechanisms of Action of Brain-Active Bacteria and Bacterial Metabolites in the Pathogenesis of Common Brain Diseases</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35807841/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:05:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35807841/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Tanja Patricia Eicher and M. Hasan Mohajeri
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract The involvement of the gut microbiota and the metabolites of colon-residing bacteria in brain disease pathogenesis has been covered in a growing number of studies, but comparative literature is scarce.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
