<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</title>
    <link>https://examplesite.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://examplesite.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 22:00:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://examplesite.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Probing the Skin-Brain Axis: New Vistas Using Mouse Models</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35806489/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 22:00:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35806489/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link MDPI link DOI
Copyright and License Information Authors: Aliće Weiglein,Evelyn Gaffal and Anne Albrecht
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract Inflammatory diseases of the skin, including atopic dermatitis and psoriasis, have gained increasing attention with rising incidences in developed countries over the past decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Euglena gracilis Promotes Lactobacillus Growth and Antioxidants Accumulation as a Potential Next-Generation Prebiotic</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35811960/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:50:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35811960/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Junjie Dai, Jiayi He, Zixi Chen, Huan Qin, Ming Du, Anping Lei, Liqing Zhao, and Jiangxin Wang
Copyright © 2022 Dai, He, Chen, Qin, Du, Lei, Zhao and Wang.
This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altered Maturation of the Skin Bacterial Communities in Infants with Atopic Dermatitis</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35818733/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:48:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35818733/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link DOI
Copyright and License Information Copyright (c) 2022 Caroline M. Olesen, Maja-Lisa Clausen, Tove Agner, Maria Asplund, Linett Rasmussen, Yasemin T. Yüksel, Paal S. Andersen, Thomas Litman, Anders J. Hansen, Christopher J. Barnes
This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.
This is an Open Access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/), allowing third parties to copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format and to remix, transform, and build upon the material for non-commercial purposes, provided proper attribution to the original work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terminalia chebula Retz. extract ameliorates the symptoms of atopic dermatitis by regulating anti-inflammatory factors in vivo and suppressing STAT1/3 and NF-ĸB signaling in vitro</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35830757/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:45:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35830757/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link DOI
Copyright and License Information Authors: Hye Jin Kim,Hyun-Kyung Song,Sun Haeng Park,Seol Jang,Ki-Sun Park,Kwang Hoon Song,Sang Kook Lee,Taesoo Kim
© 2022 The Author(s). Published by Elsevier GmbH.
This article is available under the Creative Commons CC-BY-NC-ND license and permits non-commercial use of the work as published, without adaptation or alteration provided the work is fully attributed.
Abstract Background: Terminalia chebula (TC) is a traditional medicinal plant used for treating various diseases in humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human-β-defensin-3 attenuates atopic dermatitis-like inflammation through autophagy activation and the aryl hydrocarbon receptor signaling pathway</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35834333/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:41:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35834333/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link DOI
Copyright and License Information Authors: Ge Peng, Saya Tsukamoto, Risa Ikutama, Hai Le Thanh Nguyen, Yoshie Umehara, Juan V. Trujillo-Paez, Hainan Yue, Miho Takahashi, Takasuke Ogawa, Ryoma Kishi, Mitsutoshi Tominaga, Kenji Takamori, Jiro Kitaura, Shun Kageyama, Masaaki Komatsu, Ko Okumura, Hideoki Ogawa, Shigaku Ikeda, and François Niyonsaba
Copyright © 2022, Peng et al. This work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License. To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Difference of Gut Microbiota and Their Correlations With Urinary Organic Acids Between Autistic Children With and Without Atopic Dermatitis</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35800387/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:39:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35800387/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Copyright © 2022 Hong, Hou, Xu, Lang, Jin, Zeng, Zhang, Tian and You
This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Parent-Focused Creative Approach as a Treatment for a High-Functioning Child with Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) in Korea: A Case Study</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35805495/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:36:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35805495/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Author: Jung Eun Jeanne Park
Copyright © 2022 by the author. Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract This study was conducted on a 6-year-old girl with autism spectrum disorder (ASD) in Korea. The case was initiated in February 2015, and intensive treatment was provided for one year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signalling pathways in autism spectrum disorder: mechanisms and therapeutic implications</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35817793/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:34:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35817793/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link Nature link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Chen-Chen Jiang , Li-Shan Lin , Sen Long, Xiao-Yan Ke , Kohji Fukunaga , Ying-Mei Lu and Feng Han
Open Access This article is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License, which permits use, sharing, adaptation, distribution and reproduction in any medium or format, as long as you give appropriate credit to the original author(s) and the source, provide a link to the Creative Commons license, and indicate if changes were made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GW4064 Alters Gut Microbiota Composition and Counteracts Autism-Associated Behaviors in BTBR T&#43;tf/J Mice </title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35811667/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:31:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35811667/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Jiayin Liu, Chuanqi Liu, Zhanyuan Gao, Lianyu Zhou, Junwei Gao, Yi Luo, Tianyao Liu, and Xiaotang Fan
Copyright © 2022 Liu, Liu, Gao, Zhou, Gao, Luo, Liu and Fan This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Association between cord blood metabolites in tryptophan pathway and childhood risk of autism spectrum disorder and attention-deficit hyperactivity disorder</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35810183/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:27:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35810183/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Ramkripa Raghavan, Neha S. Anand, Guoying Wang, Xiumei Hong, Colleen Pearson, Barry Zuckerman, Hehuang Xie, and Xiaobin Wang
Copyright © The Author(s) 2022
Open Access This article is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License, which permits use, sharing, adaptation, distribution and reproduction in any medium or format, as long as you give appropriate credit to the original author(s) and the source, provide a link to the Creative Commons license, and indicate if changes were made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maternal Dietary Patterns during Pregnancy and Child Autism-Related Traits: Results from Two US Cohorts</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35807909/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:24:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35807909/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Rachel Vecchione, Siwen Wang, Juliette Rando, Jorge E. Chavarro, Lisa A. Croen, M. Daniele Fallin, Irva Hertz-Picciotto, Craig J. Newschaffer, Rebecca J. Schmidt, and Kristen Lyall
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract We examined the relationship between maternal intake of established dietary patterns and child autism-related outcomes in two prospective cohorts in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Characterization of Novel Faecalibacterium prausnitzii Strains Isolated from Healthy Volunteers: A Step Forward in the Use of F. prausnitzii as a Next-Generation Probiotic</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_28713353/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:19:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_28713353/</guid>
      <description>Link to paper
Copyright and License Information Copyright © 2017 Martín, Miquel, Benevides, Bridonneau, Robert, Hudault, Chain, Berteau, Azevedo, Chatel, Sokol, Bermúdez-Humarán, Thomas and Langella.
This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) or licensor are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dietary Factors and Modulation of Bacteria Strains of Akkermansia muciniphila and Faecalibacterium prausnitzii: A Systematic Review</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_31336737/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:11:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_31336737/</guid>
      <description>Link to paper
Copyright and License Information Authors: Sanne Verhoog,1,* Petek Eylul Taneri,2 Zayne M. Roa Díaz,1 Pedro Marques-Vidal,3 John P. Troup,4 Lia Bally,5 Oscar H. Franco,1 Marija Glisic,6 and Taulant Muka1
Copyright © 2019 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract Akkermansia muciniphila and Faecalibacterium prausnitzii are highly abundant human gut microbes in healthy individuals, and reduced levels are associated with inflammation and alterations of metabolic processes involved in the development of type 2 diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overlapping Mechanisms of Action of Brain-Active Bacteria and Bacterial Metabolites in the Pathogenesis of Common Brain Diseases</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35807841/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:05:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35807841/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Tanja Patricia Eicher and M. Hasan Mohajeri
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract The involvement of the gut microbiota and the metabolites of colon-residing bacteria in brain disease pathogenesis has been covered in a growing number of studies, but comparative literature is scarce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Differences in the Gut Microbiome in Atopic Dermatitis According to the Presence of Gastrointestinal Symptoms</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35806975/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 20:37:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/pmid_35806975/</guid>
      <description>Link to paper
Copyright and License Information Authors: Chang-Yi Han, Soon-Kyeong Kwon, Mijung Yeom, Dae-Hyun Hahm, Jae-Woo Park, Hi-Joon Park, and Kyuseok Kim
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract (1) Background: Atopic dermatitis (AD) is a multifactorial chronic allergic skin disease. Gastrointestinal (GI) functions have been suggested to be associated with its incidence or severity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
