<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>diet on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</title>
    <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/tags/diet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in diet on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:24:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/tags/diet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Maternal Dietary Patterns during Pregnancy and Child Autism-Related Traits: Results from Two US Cohorts</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35807909/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:24:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35807909/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Rachel Vecchione, Siwen Wang, Juliette Rando, Jorge E. Chavarro, Lisa A. Croen, M. Daniele Fallin, Irva Hertz-Picciotto, Craig J. Newschaffer, Rebecca J. Schmidt, and Kristen Lyall
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract We examined the relationship between maternal intake of established dietary patterns and child autism-related outcomes in two prospective cohorts in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dietary Factors and Modulation of Bacteria Strains of Akkermansia muciniphila and Faecalibacterium prausnitzii: A Systematic Review</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_31336737/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:11:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_31336737/</guid>
      <description>Link to paper
Copyright and License Information Authors: Sanne Verhoog,1,* Petek Eylul Taneri,2 Zayne M. Roa Díaz,1 Pedro Marques-Vidal,3 John P. Troup,4 Lia Bally,5 Oscar H. Franco,1 Marija Glisic,6 and Taulant Muka1
Copyright © 2019 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract Akkermansia muciniphila and Faecalibacterium prausnitzii are highly abundant human gut microbes in healthy individuals, and reduced levels are associated with inflammation and alterations of metabolic processes involved in the development of type 2 diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
