<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>autism spectrum disorder on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</title>
    <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/tags/autism-spectrum-disorder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in autism spectrum disorder on A curated list of papers about autoinmune disease</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:39:11 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/tags/autism-spectrum-disorder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Difference of Gut Microbiota and Their Correlations With Urinary Organic Acids Between Autistic Children With and Without Atopic Dermatitis</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35800387/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:39:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35800387/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Copyright © 2022 Hong, Hou, Xu, Lang, Jin, Zeng, Zhang, Tian and You
This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Parent-Focused Creative Approach as a Treatment for a High-Functioning Child with Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) in Korea: A Case Study</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35805495/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:36:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35805495/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Author: Jung Eun Jeanne Park
Copyright © 2022 by the author. Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract This study was conducted on a 6-year-old girl with autism spectrum disorder (ASD) in Korea. The case was initiated in February 2015, and intensive treatment was provided for one year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signalling pathways in autism spectrum disorder: mechanisms and therapeutic implications</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35817793/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:34:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35817793/</guid>
      <description>Pubmed Link Nature link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Chen-Chen Jiang , Li-Shan Lin , Sen Long, Xiao-Yan Ke , Kohji Fukunaga , Ying-Mei Lu and Feng Han
Open Access This article is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License, which permits use, sharing, adaptation, distribution and reproduction in any medium or format, as long as you give appropriate credit to the original author(s) and the source, provide a link to the Creative Commons license, and indicate if changes were made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GW4064 Alters Gut Microbiota Composition and Counteracts Autism-Associated Behaviors in BTBR T&#43;tf/J Mice </title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35811667/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:31:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35811667/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Jiayin Liu, Chuanqi Liu, Zhanyuan Gao, Lianyu Zhou, Junwei Gao, Yi Luo, Tianyao Liu, and Xiaotang Fan
Copyright © 2022 Liu, Liu, Gao, Zhou, Gao, Luo, Liu and Fan This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License (CC BY). The use, distribution or reproduction in other forums is permitted, provided the original author(s) and the copyright owner(s) are credited and that the original publication in this journal is cited, in accordance with accepted academic practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Association between cord blood metabolites in tryptophan pathway and childhood risk of autism spectrum disorder and attention-deficit hyperactivity disorder</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35810183/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:27:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35810183/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Ramkripa Raghavan, Neha S. Anand, Guoying Wang, Xiumei Hong, Colleen Pearson, Barry Zuckerman, Hehuang Xie, and Xiaobin Wang
Copyright © The Author(s) 2022
Open Access This article is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License, which permits use, sharing, adaptation, distribution and reproduction in any medium or format, as long as you give appropriate credit to the original author(s) and the source, provide a link to the Creative Commons license, and indicate if changes were made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maternal Dietary Patterns during Pregnancy and Child Autism-Related Traits: Results from Two US Cohorts</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35807909/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:24:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35807909/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Rachel Vecchione, Siwen Wang, Juliette Rando, Jorge E. Chavarro, Lisa A. Croen, M. Daniele Fallin, Irva Hertz-Picciotto, Craig J. Newschaffer, Rebecca J. Schmidt, and Kristen Lyall
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract We examined the relationship between maternal intake of established dietary patterns and child autism-related outcomes in two prospective cohorts in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overlapping Mechanisms of Action of Brain-Active Bacteria and Bacterial Metabolites in the Pathogenesis of Common Brain Diseases</title>
      <link>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35807841/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:05:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordimontana82.github.io/autoinmune-papers/pmid_35807841/</guid>
      <description>Link
Copyright and License Information Authors: Tanja Patricia Eicher and M. Hasan Mohajeri
Copyright © 2022 by the authors.
Licensee MDPI, Basel, Switzerland. This article is an open access article distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution (CC BY) license (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).
Abstract The involvement of the gut microbiota and the metabolites of colon-residing bacteria in brain disease pathogenesis has been covered in a growing number of studies, but comparative literature is scarce.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
